OGADA STANLEY CHINEDU



Contact

Phone:

+234 807 791 7051

Email:

chineduogada@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/chineduogada/

Person Data

Date of Birth:

October 10, 2000

Nationality:

Nigerian

State of Origin:

Abia

Local Govt. Area:

Isuikwuato

State:

Lagos

Address:

13a Laduba Street, Okokomaiko, Ojo, Lagos state (102101).

Marital Status:

Single

Sex:

Male

Summary

I am **Full Stack Web Developer** specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous technologies including: **JavaScript**, **React / Next.js**, **Node.js / Express.js**, **MongoDB**. I carry out quality assurance **tests** to discover errors and optimize usability.

I am well skilled and open to learn new technologies. I am looking forward to working with a good team.

Skills Highlights

- HTML / CSS / JS (Es6+)
- React.js / Next.js
- Jest / Testing-library/react
- Git / Github / Markdown
- Vercel (deployment)
- Node.js / Express.js
- MongoDB / Mongoose / Redis
- Puppeteer
- Postman / VS Code
- Heroku etc.

Experience

Front-end Engineer - 10/2020 to present

MY-PORTFOLIO (still under development) - Lagos

I developed the UI of this web application with **React.js / Next.js** and **ContextAPI** for global state management.

Links to this project:

- https://my-portfolio-drgt0dsn2.vercel.app/
- https://github.com/chineduogada/my-portfolio

Front-end Engineer - 09/2020 to present

REACT-RAPID-CAROUSEL (npm) – Lagos

I developed the UI of this *npm* package with **React.js** (create-react-library) and **Styled-components.**

Links to this project:

- https://www.npmjs.com/package/react-rapid-carousel
- https://github.com/chineduogada/react-rapid-carousel

Full-stack Engineer - 08/2020 to present

SELLIT.NG – Lagos

- I developed the API of SELLIT Application with **Node.js**, **Express.js** and **MongoDB / Mongoose.js**.
- I developed the UI of the library with **React.js** and **ContextAPI** for global state management.

Link to this project: https://github.com/chineduogada/sellit

Education

Bachelor of Science (BSc): **Computer Science** – 2017-2020 **Les Cours Sonou University**, Benin Republic, Cotonou